aus.com 2019-11-14

# Allied Universal Privacy Policy and Information Collection

### Our Policy

Allied Universal ("we" or "us") respects and understands its customers' concerns about confidentiality and privacy, and we take reasonable steps to ensure that any information you give us is handled in a safe and responsible manner. Because of our respect and understanding, we have developed this Privacy Policy which discloses the privacy practices of Allied Universal and describes the information we collect about you during your use of the Website and what use we may make of that information.

It is important to remember that by using our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We suggest that you refer to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis as it may change, at any time in Allied Universal's sole discretion, in order to allow us to take advantage of technological advances or for business purposes or legal reasons.  

### Information Collection and Usage

We do not sell, lend or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third parties outside of the Company, its affiliates, subsidiaries, authorized agents and service providers, operating companies and other related entities.

If you supply us with your e-mail or mailing address, you may receive occasional mail from us announcing services or promotional events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please send us an e-mail to [info@aus.com](mailto:info@aus.com) indicating your e-mail address or mailing address as applicable and asking us to remove you from our mailing list.

We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you as required by law, including voluntary disclosures to law enforcement agencies and government officials, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

In the event the Company is ever sold, we reserve the right to transfer ownership of our e-mail list and other personally identifiable information to the acquiring company. Should this happen, we will instruct the new owners of the company to contact users via e-mail to notify you of the change.

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), third parties may unlawfully intercept or access files, transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.  

### Third Party Collectors of Information

Our Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that your information is disclosed by you to third parties, whether our clients, service providers, advertisers or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of your information. These third parties adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Because we do not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We do not make any representations or warranties as to how such third parties may use your information.  

### Notification of Material Changes to this Policy

This Section identifies material changes to this Policy since the Effective Date.

None at present.  

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to review, change or remove your personal information, you can e-mail us at [info@aus.com](mailto:info@aus.com). Additionally, you can contact us by writing to:  
Allied Universal, 8 Tower Bridge, 161 Washington Street, Suite 600, Conshohocken, PA 19428.
